A Guide to the Markle Foundation records, Record Group 1-Record Group 3 FA024
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Markle Foundation Programs, 1
  - Markle Foundation Programs - Accession 2, 2; 24 Cubic Feet
    - Grants in Communications (1979-1984), 1975-1994; 1; 13.2 cu. ft. Cubic Feet 11 boxes
      - Cleveland State University - Sidney Kraus, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 73)
        D80223.
      - Cleveland State University - Sidney Kraus, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 74)
        G80328
      - Cleveland State University - Sidney Kraus, 1981-1982, 1984, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 75)
        D82106.
      - Cleveland State University - Sidney Kraus, 1984-1988 (Box 4, Folder 76)
        D85110.
      - University of Colorado, Boulder - National Alliance of Media Arts Centers Conference, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 77)
        D80332.
      - University of Colorado, Boulder - National Alliance of Media Arts Centers Conference, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 78)
        D80332. Printed material.
      - Consumer Interest Research Institute - Mary Gardiner Jones, 1984-1987 (Box 4, Folder 79)
        D85111.
      - Council on Foundations - Elizabeth T. Boris, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 80)
        D84217.
      - Council on Foundations - Elizabeth T. Boris, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 81)
      - Council on Foundations - Elizabeth T. Boris, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 82)
      - Cultural Council Foundation - Susan Eenigenburg, 1977, 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 83)
        G81218.
      - Cultural Council Foundation - Susan Eenigenburg, 1977, 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 84)
      - Cultural Council Foundation - Sara P. Garretson, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 85)
        D81226.
      - Cultural Council Foundation - Independent Cinema Artists and Producers - Brian Kahin, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 86)
        D83113.
      - Cultural Council Foundation - Independent Cinema Artists and Producers - Brian Kahin, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 87)
      - Dalhousie University - Jennifer K. Bankier, 1983-1989 (Box 4, Folder 88)
        D83335.
      - Dalhousie University - Jennifer K. Bankier, 1983-1989 (Box 4, Folder 89)
        D83335. Papers and articles.
      - Dalhousie University - Jennifer K. Bankier, 1983-1989 (Box 4, Folder 90)
      - Duke University - J. David Barber, 1980-1986 (Box 4, Folder 91)
        G80101.
      - Duke University - J. David Barber, 1980-1986 (Box 4, Folder 92)
      - Duke University - Henry Geller, 1981-1985 (Box 4, Folder 93)
        G81213.
      - Duke University - Henry Geller, 1981-1985 (Box 4, Folder 94)
        G81213. Legal papers.
      - Duke University - Henry Geller, 1981-1985 (Box 4, Folder 95)
      - Duke University - Henry Geller, 1981-1985 (Box 4, Folder 96)
      - Duke University - Washington Center for Policy Research - Dale Hatfield, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 97)
        G82218. Cancelled.
      - Duke University - David Barber, 1982-1987 (Box 4, Folder 98)
        G83223.
      - Duke University - Robert Entman, 1984-1989 (Box 4, Folder 99)
        64/1043.
      - Duke University - Washington Center for Policy Research - Henry Geller, 1984-1988 (Box 4, Folder 100)
        65/1010.
      - Eastern Public Radio Network - Julie Crockford, 1981-1984 (Box 5, Folder 101)
        G81215.
      - Eastern Public Radio Network - Julie Crockford, 1981-1984 (Box 5, Folder 102)
        G81215. Newsletters.
      - Eastern Public Radio Network - Julie Crockford, 1981-1984 (Box 5, Folder 103)
        G81215. Financial statements.
      - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - WNET/Channel 13 - Stephen L. Salyer, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 104)
        D83229.
      - Emory University - Ellen Mickiewicz, 1984-1985, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 105)
        61/1041.
      - Family Radio Programming, Inc. - Program-Related Investment, 1981-1984 (Box 5, Folder 106)
      - Family Radio Programming, Inc. - Program-Related Investment, 1981-1984 (Box 5, Folder 107)
      - Family Radio Programming, Inc. - Program-Related Investment, 1981-1984 (Box 5, Folder 108)
      - Family Radio Programming, Inc. - Program-Related Investment, 1981-1984 (Box 5, Folder 109)
      - Family Radio Programming, Inc. - Program-Related Investment, 1981-1984 (Box 5, Folder 110)
      - Family Radio Programming, Inc. - Program-Related Investment - Securied Notes and Agreements, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 111)
      - Family Radio Programming, Inc. - Program-Related Investment - Final Accounts Payable, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 112)
      - Family Radio Programming, Inc. - Program-Related Investment - Legal, 1982-1988 (Box 5, Folder 113)
      - Family Radio Programming, Inc. - General Mills Foundation/NEA Grants, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 114)
      - Family Radio Programming, Inc. - NEA Grant, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 115)
      - Family Radio Programming, Inc. - George Morency and Miles Siegel, 1984-1987 (Box 5, Folder 116)
        G84009PRI.
      - Foreign Policy Association - Jim Talbot, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 117)
        D82108.
      - Foundation Center, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 118)
        D81222.
      - Foundation Center, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 119)
        D82109.
      - Foundation Center, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 120)
        D83111.
      - Foundation Center, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 121)
        D84107.
      - George Washington University - Michael Robinson, 1982-1986 (Box 5, Folder 122)
        G83104.
      - George Washington University - Michael Robinson, 1982-1986 (Box 5, Folder 123)
        G83104. Articles.
      - Greater Washington Educational Telecommunications Association - WETA Radio - Anne Heyniger, 1980-1984 (Box 5, Folder 124)
        D83227.
      - Greater Washington Educational Telecommunications Association - WETA Radio - Anne Heyniger, 1980-1984 (Box 5, Folder 125)
        D83227. Printed material.
      - Harvard University - Graduate School of Education - Laurene Meringoff, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 126)
        D82110.
      - Harvard University - Anthony Oettinger, 1981-1988, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 128)
        G82329. Articles and publications.
      - Harvard University - Anthony Oettinger, 1981-1988, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 129)
      - Harvard University - Institute of Politics - Jonathan Moore, 1983-1989 (Box 5, Folder 130)
        G83332.
      - Harvard University - Anthony Oettinger, 1981-1988, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 127)
        G82329.
      - Harvard University - Institute of Politics - Jonathan Moore, 1983-1989 (Box 6, Folder 131)
      - Harvard University - Institute of Politics - Jonathan Moore, 1983-1989 (Box 6, Folder 132)
        G83332. Papers and publications.
      - Harvard University - Institute of Politics - Jonathan Moore, 1983-1989 (Box 6, Folder 133)
      - Harvard University - Hebrew University of Jerusalem - Gavriel Salomon, 1982-1985 (Box 6, Folder 134)
        G83338.
      - Hastings Center - Daniel Callahan, 1981-1985 (Box 6, Folder 135)
        G83102.
      - Hastings Center - Daniel Callahan, 1981-1985 (Box 6, Folder 136)
      - Hebrew University of Jerusalem - Elihu Katz, 1978-1984, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 137)
        G80025.
      - Howard University - Tenth Annual Telecommunications Policy Research Conference - Oscar H. Gandy, Jr., 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 138)
        D82330.
      - Independent Sector, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 139)
        D82333.
      - Independent Sector - Beverly With, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 140)
        D83228.
      - Independent Sector - Beverly With, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 141)
        D84218.
      - Indiana University Foundation - David Weaver, 1980-1983 (Box 6, Folder 142)
        D81111.
      - Institute for Information Policy - Harry M. Shooshan III and Michael Rice, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 143)
        G83105.
      - Institute for Information Policy - Harry M. Shooshan III and Michael Rice, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 144)
        G83105. Articles and publications.
      - Institute for Information Policy - Harry M. Shooshan III and Michael Rice, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 145)
      - Institute for Journalism Education - Nancy Hicks, 1981-1984 (Box 6, Folder 146)
        D82219.
      - University of Iowa - Gilbert Cranberg, 1981-1984 (Box 6, Folder 147)
        G83103.
      - University of Iowa - Gilbert Cranberg, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 148)
        60/1040.
      - Jackson Community College - Michael T. Joyce and J. David Bolter, 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 149)
        G85105.
      - KCET, Los Angeles, 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 150)
        D80224.
      - KOPN Community Radio - Midwest Radio Theatre Workshop - Susan Newstead, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 151)
        D83112.
      - London Graduate School of Business Studies - Andrew Ehrenberg, 1980-1981, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 152)
        G81221.
      - London Graduate School of Business Studies - Andrew Ehrenberg, 1982-1987 (Box 6, Folder 153)
        G83107.
      - London School of Economics and Political Science - Hilde Himmelweit, 1983-1989 (Box 6, Folder 154)
        D84110.
      - Markle Foundation - Media Commentary Council, Inc. - "Channels" magazine, 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 155)
        G80212.
      - Markle Foundation - Television Conference Foundation - Gene Accas, 1979-1986 (Box 6, Folder 156)
        G80215.
      - Markle Foundation - University of California, Los Angeles - Jeffrey Alexander, 1980-1981, 1982, 1984, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 157)
        D81110.
      - Markle Foundation - Children's Radio Conference, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 158)
        D81228.
      - Markle Foundation - Thomas Patterson Book Distribution, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 159)
        D81230.
      - Markle Foundation - Conference on New Media in the Home - Richard Heffner, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 160)
        D81339.
      - Markle Foundation - TMC Multimedia Corporation, 1982-1985 (Box 7, Folder 161)
        G82040-PRI.
      - Markle Foundation - Children's Radio - Georg Morency and Miles Siegel, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 162)
        G82102.
      - Markle Foundation - University of Pennsylvania - Wharton School, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 163)
        D83116.
      - Markle Foundation - TMC Multimedia Corporation, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 164)
        D83224.
      - Markle Foundation, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 165)
        D83231. Eli Rubinstein meeting on children and television.
      - Markle Foundation - "Impact of Television on Children", 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 166)
        84-29. Meeting expenses.
      - Markle Foundation - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies Evaluation - Janet Morgan, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 167)
        D84113.
      - Markle Foundation, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 168)
        D84114. Computer conferencing.
      - University of Maryland - John Robinson, 1982-1986 (Box 7, Folder 169)
        D82339.
      - University of Maryland - Judith Lichtenberg, 1983-1990 (Box 7, Folder 170)
        G85104.
      - University of Maryland - Judith Lichtenberg, 1983-1990 (Box 7, Folder 171)
        G85104. Papers.
      - University of Maryland - Judith Lichtenberg, 1983-1990 (Box 7, Folder 172)
      - University of Maryland - Judith Lichtenberg, 1983-1990 (Box 7, Folder 173)
        G85104. Printed material.
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Eighth Annual Telecommunications Policy Research Conference, 1978-1984 (Box 7, Folder 174)
        D80221.
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - W. Russell Neuman, 1980, 1981, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 175)
        D80222.
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Ithiel de Sola Pool, 1980-1986 (Box 7, Folder 176)
        G81105.
      - University of Massachusetts, Amherst - Daniel R. Anderson, 1982-1986 (Box 7, Folder 177)
        G83109.
      - University of Massachusetts, Amherst - Daniel R. Anderson, 1982-1986 (Box 7, Folder 178)
        G83109. Background material.
      - Media Commentary Council, Inc. - "Channels" Magazine, 1979, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 179)
        G82214.
      - Media Commentary Council, Inc. - "Channels" Magazine, 1979, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 180)
        G82214. Publicity articles.
      - Media Commentary Council, Inc. - "Channels" Magazine, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 181)
        G83219.
      - Media Commentary Council, Inc. - "Channels" Magazine, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 182)
        G84102.
      - University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, 1980-1981, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 183)
        D81225.
      - Minnesota Public Radio - William Kling, 1981-1984 (Box 7, Folder 184)
        G82104.
      - Minnesota Public Radio - William Kling, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 185)
        D83117.
      - University of Minnesota - National News Council Transfer, 1984, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 186)
        69/1046.
      - Mitre Corporation/City of Cincinnati - William Mason and Sylvester Murray, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 187)
        G85101.
      - Moving Image, Inc. - Film Forum - Karen Cooper, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 188)
        G81217.
      - National Citizens Committee for Broadcasting - Samuel A. Simon, 1981-1985 (Box 7, Folder 189)
        D82112.
        National Black Media Coalition.
      - National Citizens Committee for Broadcasting - Samuel A. Simon, 1981-1985 (Box 7, Folder 190)
        D82112. Press releases and memoranda.
      - National Council for Children and Television, 1979-1983 (Box 7, Folder 191)
        G80329.
      - National Federation of Community Broadcasters - Thomas J. Thomas, 1980-1983 (Box 8, Folder 192)
        G81102.
      - National Federation of Community Broadcasters - Thomas J. Thomas, 1980-1983 (Box 8, Folder 193)
        G81102. Newsletters and news releases.
      - National Federation of Community Broadcasters - Thomas J. Thomas, 1983-1986 (Box 8, Folder 194)
        G84104.
      - National Federation of Community Broadcasters - Thomas J. Thomas, 1983-1986 (Box 8, Folder 195)
        G84104. Printed material.
      - National Federation of Local Cable Programmers - Low Power Television Hotline Project, 1980-1985 (Box 8, Folder 196)
        D81224.
      - National Federation of Local Cable Programmers - Low Power Television Hotline Project, 1980-1985 (Box 8, Folder 197)
        D81224. Background material.
      - National Federation of Local Cable Programmers - Low Power Television Hotline Project, 1980-1985 (Box 8, Folder 198)
        D81224. Printed material.
      - National Federation of Local Cable Programmers - Low Power Television Hotline Project - Pat Watkins, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 199)
        D82225.
      - National Federation of Local Cable Programmers - Low Power Television Hotline Project - Pat Watkins, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 200)
        D82225. Background and printed material.
      - National Federation of Local Cable Programmers - Low Power Television Hotline Project - Pat Watkins, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 201)
      - National Foundation for the Improvement of Education, 1982-1985, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 202)
        G85106.
      - National Foundation for the Improvement of Education, 1982-1985, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 203)
        G85106. Background material.
      - National News Council - Norman Isaacs, 1973-1984 (Box 8, Folder 204)
        G80102.
      - National News Council - Norman Isaacs, 1973-1984 (Box 8, Folder 205)
        G80102. Background and printed material.
      - National News Council - Norman Isaacs, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 206)
        G82326.
      - National News Council - Norman Isaacs, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 207)
        G82326. Background material.
      - National News Council - Lucy Benson and Richard Salant, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 208)
        G83337.
      - National News Council - Lucy Benson and Richard Salant, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 209)
        G83337. Background and printed material.
      - National Public Radio - Ronald Bornstein, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 210)
        D84112.
      - Native American Public Broadcasting Consortium - Frank Blythe, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 211)
        D82107.
      - Native American Public Broadcasting Consortium - Frank Blythe, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 212)
        D82107. Background material.
      - Native American Public Broadcasting Consortium - Frank Blythe, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 213)
      - Native American Public Broadcasting Consortium - Frank Blythe, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 214)
        D82334.
      - Native American Public Broadcasting Consortium - Frank Blythe, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 215)
        D82334. Report.
      - New Dimensions Foundation - Michael Toms, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 216)
        G81103.
      - New Dimensions Foundation - Michael Toms, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 217)
        G81103. Interim report.
      - New Dimensions Foundation - Michael Toms, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 218)
        G81103. Final report.
      - New Dimensions Foundation - Justine Toms, 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 219)
        D82335.
      - New York City - City Planning Department, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 220)
        D80331.
      - New York City - City Planning Department, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 221)
        D80331. Report.
      - New York University - Institute for the Humanities - Mary Douglas and Karen Steinmetz, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 222)
        D81109.
      - New York University - Institute for the Humanities - Mary Douglas and Karen Steinmetz, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 223)
        D81227.
      - New York University - School of the Arts - Michael Miller, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 224)
        D81340.
      - New York World Television Festival, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 225)
        D81108.
      - New York World Television Festival - Thomas Madigan, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 226)
        D85114.
      - North Carolina Agency for Public Telecommunications - Lee Wing, 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 227)
        G84208.
      - Northwestern University - Robert Pekurny, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 228)
        D80334.
      - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund - Kathy Bonk, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 229)
        G81220.
      - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund - Kathy Bonk, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 230)
        G81220. Background material.
      - University of Pennsylvania - Wharton School - Ronald E. Frank and Marshall G. Greenburg, 1980-1985 (Box 9, Folder 232)
        G80213.
      - University of Pennsylvania - Annenberg School of Communications - Barry Cole, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 233)
        D81336.
      - Public Agenda Foundation - Daniel Yankelovich, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 234)
        G81219.
      - Public Agenda Foundation - Jean Johnson, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 235)
        G82216.
      - Public Agenda Foundation - Daniel Yankelovich and Jean Johnson, 1984-1989 (Box 9, Folder 236)
        58/1023.
      - Public Agenda Foundation - Daniel Yankelovich and Jean Johnson, 1984-1989 (Box 9, Folder 237)
        58/1023. Evaluations.
      - Public Agenda Foundation - Daniel Yankelovich and Jean Johnson, 1984-1989 (Box 9, Folder 238)
        58/1023. Printed material.
      - Public Communication, Inc. - Seymour Feshbach, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 239)
        G81116.
      - Public Communication, Inc. - Seymour Feshbach, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 240)
        D83110.
      - Public Communication, Inc. - Seymour Feshbach, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 241)
        D83342.
      - Public Communication, Inc. - Seymour Feshbach, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 242)
        D85108.
      - Public Interest Communications Service - William W. Harris, 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 243)
        G80219.
      - Radio Foundation, Inc. - Larry Josephson, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 244)
        D81223.
      - Radio Foundation, Inc. - Larry Josephson, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 245)
        D81223. Corporation for Public Broadcasting grant application.
      - Radio Foundation, Inc. - Larry Josephson, 1983-1986 (Box 9, Folder 246)
        D84111.
      - RAND Corporation - Stanley M. Besen and Leland L. Johnson, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 247)
        G82101.
      - RAND Corporation - Stanley M. Besen and Leland L. Johnson, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 248)
        G82101. Final report.
      - RAND Corporation - Stanley M. Besen and Leland L. Johnson, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 249)
        G82101. Background material.
      - RAND Corporation - Stanley M. Besen and Leland L. Johnson, 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 250)
        G83221.
      - RAND Corporation - Stanley M. Besen and Leland L. Johnson, 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 251)
        G83221. Final report.
      - RAND Corporation - Stanley M. Besen and Leland L. Johnson, 1982-1985 (Box 10, Folder 252)
        G83221. Reports and papers.
      - RAND Corporation - Stanley M. Besen and Leland L. Johnson, 1982-1985 (Box 10, Folder 253)
      - Research Communications, Inc. - George Morency, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 254)
        D82111.
      - University of Richmond - Robert S. Alley and Irby B. Brown, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 255)
        D80111.
      - University of Richmond - Robert S. Alley and Irby B. Brown, 1979-1986 (Box 10, Folder 256)
        G80214.
      - University of Richmond - Robert S. Alley and Irby B. Brown, 1979-1981, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 257)
        D80220.
      - Roosevelt Center - Christopher Arterton, 1982-1988 (Box 10, Folder 258)
        G83333.
      - Scientists' Institute for Public Information - Fred Jerome, 1979-1984 (Box 10, Folder 259)
        G80330.
      - Scientists' Institute for Public Information - Fred Jerome, 1979-1984 (Box 10, Folder 260)
        G80330. Report.
      - Scientists' Institute for Public Information - Fred Jerome, 1979-1984 (Box 10, Folder 261)
        G80330. Printed material.
      - Social Science Research Council - Kenneth Prewitt, 1983-1988 (Box 10, Folder 262)
        G84101.
      - Society for Neuroscience - Neal Miller and Marjorie Wilson, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 263)
        D76009.
      - Society for Neuroscience - Neal Miller and Marjorie Wilson, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 264)
        D76009. Seminar proceedings.
      - Southern Educational Communications Association - Pat Conner, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 265)
        D82222.
      - Southern Educational Communications Association - Pat Conner, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 266)
        G82328.
      - Southern Educational Communications Association - Pat Conner, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 267)
      - Southern Illinois University - Charles H. Harpole, 1980-1982, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 268)
        D80335.
      - Southern Illinois University - Charles H. Harpole, 1980-1982, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 269)
        D80335. Conference proceedings.
      - Southern Regional Conference - Steve Suitts, 1981-1987 (Box 10, Folder 270)
        G82105.
      - Speech Communications Association - Robert K. Avery, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 271)
        D84219.
      - Stanford University - Donald F. Roberts and Gavriel Salomon, 1978-1983 (Box 10, Folder 272)
        G80104.
      - Stanford University - Donald F. Roberts and Gavriel Salomon, 1978-1983 (Box 10, Folder 273)
      - Stanford University - Donald F. Roberts, 1979-1982 (Box 10, Folder 274)
        D80107.
      - Stanford University - Donald F. Roberts, 1982-1988 (Box 10, Folder 275)
        G83106.
      - Stanford University - Donald F. Roberts, 1984-1987 (Box 10, Folder 276)
        G83338 transferred to G83106.
      - Stony Brook Foundation of State University of New York at Stony Brook - John H. Gagnon and Cathy Greenblat, 1979-1981, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 277)
        D80336.
      - Tel Aviv University, 1984-1988 (Box 10, Folder 278)
        G83338 transferred to 68/1045.
      - Television Audience Assessment, Inc. - Elizabeth Roberts, 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 279)
        G81212.
      - Television Audience Assessment, Inc. - Elizabeth Roberts, 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 280)
        G81212. Background material.
      - Television Audience Assessment, Inc. - Elizabeth Roberts, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 281)
        D81229.
      - Television Audience Assessment, Inc. - Elizabeth Roberts, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 282)
        G82215.
      - Television Audience Assessment, Inc. - Elizabeth Roberts, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 283)
        G83218.